Guide to the A Gathering of the Tribes Records MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Audiovisual Recordings, 1983-2011; 13 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 unknown profile containers, and 4 items in a shared cassette box.; 18.99 Gigabytes in 11 computer files; 305 items on audio and video carriers.
  - Subseries I.A. Video, 1983-2011
    - Dallas Slam Team at Tribes, March 7 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0033)
      Currently no acces copy is available.
    - Dallas Slam Team at Tribes, March 7 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0108)
    - Peoples Poetry Gathering, Poetry Project, Tape 2, April 11 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0011, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0011)
    - Poetry Project, Tape 1, April 11 1999; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0193, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0193)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 118 min.
    - Skyscrapers, Taxis & Tampons; Readings at Tribes & Thirteen, May 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0002, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0002)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 83 min. Preservation Note: Recorded in low light.
    - March on Pentagon - Demonstrations in Washington, June 5 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Filmed by Dr. Ljubo Vujovic" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0042, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0042)
    - Tribes "Bird Nite" Tape 1 of 2, August 26 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:00:00 (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0016, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0016)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 60 min. Preservation Note: Camera information visible on source tape.
    - Tribes "Bird Nite" Tape 2 of 2, August 26 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:27:00; Cassette annotation: "Bird Fest Tribes" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0067, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0067)
    - Skyscrapers, Taxis & Tampons, 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "video by [Murill]" (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0102, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0102)
    - Sweet Love, Bitter, 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:32:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial Release (Rhapsody Films, Inc.). (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0029)
    - Earth Bird Presents: Poetry in the Garden, 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0112, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0112)
    - Ishmael Reed Reader March 30 / Morgan Stanley, John Farris 3/6/00, March 6 and 30 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0128, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0128)
    - Quincy Troupe - Tribes, April 2 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0127, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0127)
    - Bob H, Rax B, John Farris, Bobby G. - Opening at Tribes, May 6 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0126, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0126)
    - Staten Island Ferry / Hart Magazine Show, August 8 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0107, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0107)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 150 min.
    - National Slam Festival, August 12 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0152, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0152)
    - Charlie Parker Festival, August 24 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0059, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0059)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 69 min.
    - Lorenzo Pace Sculpture Unveiling, October 19 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Recorded by Paul A. [Horea]" (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0209, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0209)
      Four 4x6 photos were separated from the cassette sleeve into Series III: Project Files.
    - Ute Schindler - Opening @ A Gathering of the Tribes, November 4 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0171, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0171)
    - Gathering of the Tribes Release Party, November 9 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Note attached to cassette sleve: "Tapes for Steve". (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0063, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0063)
    - Underground Fest @ Tribes Pt 1 & 2, November 11 2000; 1 media elements (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0180, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0180)
    - Jazz on a Summer's Day, 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:30:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Bert Sterns Productions / New Yorker Films Artwork). (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0316)
    - The Real Deal, 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:27:00; Commercial Release (The Cinema Guild, Inc.).; Label: "a short film about war written by Marc Levy".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0207)
    - Hettie Jones at Tribes / Underground Fest at Tribes Pt 3, circa 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Cassette has same batch number as cassette 198.0063, which was dated 2000. (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0064, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0064)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 123 min.
    - Butch Morris: Global Fax Festival, circa 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0166, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0166)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 65 min., Preservation Note: Picture quality is poor.
    - Steve Cannon interview with Penny Arcade, February 27 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Note on cassette sleeve: "Interview that was made w/ Steve" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0037, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0037)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 102 min., Preservation Note: Camera information visible on source tape.
    - Clock, by Ron Keefer, April 16 2001; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0249, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0249)
    - The Body of Loretta, April 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Tribes, J. Liotta" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0070, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0070)
    - The Descendants of Africa, June 14 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:09:05; Commercial Release (W.E.T. Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0213)
    - A Gathering of the Tribes Tenth Anniversary Celebration on the Occasion of The Charlie Parker Festival, August 29 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0116, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0116)
    - L'Humor i la Rabia, 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0015)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon - Outtakes, [October 20 2002]; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial / promotional release (Berko Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0299)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon, October 20 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial / promotional release (Berko Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0198)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon, October 20 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial / promotional release (Berko Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0196)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon October 20, 2002 / Howl!, 2003, 2002-2003; cuid40336 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_10)
    - Chinese Musicians, November 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0165, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0165)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 59 min.
    - The Jerome Reading Series Presents: Christina Chiu & Lourdes Vazquez with musical interludes by Ji Hong, at Tribes, December 1 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "funded in part by the Jerome Foundation"; "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0132, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0132)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 98 min.
    - Iberian Tribes, December 6 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:00:00; Label annotation: "Susan L. Yung" (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0133, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0133)
    - Mighty Times: The Legacy of Rosa Parks, 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:40:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Southern Poverty Law Center). (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0267)
    - Mighty Times: The Legacy of Rosa Parks, 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:40:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial Release (Southern Poverty Law Center). (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0268)
    - Alcatraz is Not an Island, 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:56:40; Commercial Release (ITVS).; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0048)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial Release. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0242)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial Release. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0243)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial release. (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.0317)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial release. (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.0318)
    - Poetry Show: Billy Bang, January 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0237, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0237)
    - Poetry Show: Steve [Del...] & Yuko [Oto..] / Billy [Bang], January 2003; 1 media elements; Label inside cassette sleeve torn in half. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0236, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0236)
    - Tribes 1) 2/16/03 2) Charles Wright 3/2/03 "The Wig" BK party, February - March 2003; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0224, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0224)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 74 min.
    - Tribes 3-14-03 - Closing Party / 3-16-03 - Poetry Reading - Anyssa Kim, Wang Pang & Kamiko Hahn (No Show), March 14 & 16 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0208, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0208)
    - Tribes Art Opening @ Indian Music & 'Voices'; Artists: Bridget Galway, Kara Williamson, March 21 2003; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0211, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0211)
    - Tribes @ Sarah Lawrence 4-11-03 / Tribes @ Bowery Poetry Club 4-21-03 / Unbearables @ Tribes 5-2-03, April - May 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0241, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0241)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 232 min.
    - Tribes @ Nuyorican Poets Cafe - w/ Anyssa Kim, Vong, Lourdes Vargas, May 14 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0239, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0239)
    - Carl Hancock Rux @ Visions Festival, May 21 2003; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0222, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0222)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 39 min.
    - Tribes @ Cornelia St. Cafe: Dawoud on Sitar; Poets - Anyssa Kim & Nadine Mozon, June 4 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0256, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0256)
    - Tribes - Pedro Pietri, Onome Djere & Tom Savage / The Reggie Nicholson Trio w/ Kalaparush McIntyer, Brian Smith, July 6 2003; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0260, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0260)
      Flyer removed from original cassette sleeve and housed in series.
    - Oops, July 12 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0246, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0246)
    - Tribes @ Blue Stockings Bookstore: "Oops" by Steve Cannon; Barbara Purcell; & Anyssa Kim, July 15 2003; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0206, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0206)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 47 min.
    - Free Tibet @ Tribes, July 27 2003; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0258, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0258)
    - Oops; Mia Kim's "Fashion Madness" & [J]ong @ Tribes, August 7 2003; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0221, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0221)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 72 minutes.
    - Tribes @ Nuyorican Poets Cafe with Anyssa Kim & Blackout @ Grand Army Plaza, August 13 2003; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0201, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0201)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 114 min.
    - Yuko Fujimama Trio w/ Roy Campbell & Reggie Nicholson @ Tribes, August 17 2003; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0238, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0238)
    - Jazzmobile with Hilton Ruiz @ Tribes, August 25 2003; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0202, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0202)
    - Charlie Parker Exhibit @ Tribes, August 29 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0226, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0226)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 88 min.
    - Chorus of Poets, conducted by Butch Morris, Bowery Poetry Club, September 2003; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0220, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0220)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 51 min.
    - Anyssa Kim Book Party @ Bowery Poetry Club, October 2003; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0214, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0214)
    - 12-11-03 - Brian Leo @ Tribes / 1-23-04 Michael Tong's Tea Party @ Tribes (Chinese New Year), circa 1990-2007; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0265, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0265)
    - Howl, December 17 2003; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0244, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0244)
    - Wynton Marsalis: Up Close and Personal, 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:00:00 (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0007, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0007)
    - Gulsen Calik @ Tribes - Closing / Lois Elaine Griffith @ Tribes about Pedro Pietri, March 7 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0200, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0200)
    - El Negro Mas Chulo: African by Legacy, Mexican by Birth - Ayana v. Jackson & Marco Villalobos, April 10 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0215, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0215)
    - 5-2-04 - Huang Xiang @ Tribes / 5-6-04 - Yusef Komunyakaa & Wang Ping @ Tribes, May 2 & 6 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0257, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0257)
    - ChrisTwomey, Art and Genetics in a Digital Age - Artists Talk on Art - PANEL DISCUSSION, May 21 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0274, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0274)
    - Jazz Mobile @ Tribes w/ Ed Vega, May 22 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "By Susan L. Yung". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0269, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0269)
    - Vision Festival 9 - NY Skyscraper, conducted by Butch Morris, May 31 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "video by Susan L. Yung". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0203, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0203)
    - ChrisTwomey, OMNI SERIES - Art and Genetics in a Digital Age - CNN, Jeanne Moos, June 3 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:01:30; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0279)
    - 7-9-04 Sabir Mateen & Susan L. Yung @ 128 Rivington Gallery / 6-19-04 - Dor Green @ Tribes "William", June - July 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0263, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0263)
    - First Queens International Poetry Festival, 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0280, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0280)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 124 min., Preservation note: "unstable signal"
    - 2-12-05 - Tribes - John Ranard & Chin Chin Yang / 2-19-05 - Evie Ivy's "Dance of the Word", February 12 & 19 2005; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0292, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0292)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 8 hrs. 7 min.
    - Butch Morris conducts: A Chorus of Poets, at Nuyorican Poets Cafe, June 28 2005; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0293, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0293)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 8 hrs 7 min.
    - Wasman Productions Movies -- So Many Galleries, and Kandinsky Bootlegged, circa 2010; cuid40341 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_8)
    - Event -- Blood Ballet Cabaret, 2011-12-09; cuid40340 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_14)
    - Anger Management -- Cindy Performance, undated; cuid40337 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_11)
    - Event -- Behind the Mascara by Eva Brownies, undated; cuid40338 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_12)
    - Movie -- Lawrence D. "Butch" Morris Black, undated; cuid40342 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_9)
    - Interview and Art Opening -- Herb & Kitty Katzenjammer's Kollection of Kontemporary Konceptual Art, undated; cuid40339 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_198_ER_13)
    - [Commercial copy W.C. Fields / 3 Classics], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Video Treasures, Inc.). (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0253)
    - [Commercial copy Backbone of the World], 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:56:06; By George Burdeau; Preview release (Independent Television Service).; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0134)
    - [Commercial copy Silent Movie], 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:27:00; Commercial Release (20th Century Fox).; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0047)
    - [Off-air television recording of ABC News Nightline: Viewpoint: Crime, Violence and TV News], December 10 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial Release (MPI Home Video).; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0088)
    - [Off-air television recording of Angel Heart], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; No labels or annotations on cassette. Title transcribed from cassette sleeve. (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0023)
    - [Off-air television recording of CSPAN], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0251)
      Label: "All By Myself", Norman Loftis"
    - [Off-air television recording of CSPAN, Sunday-Monday, July 10th / 11th], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0300)
    - [Off-air television recording of Firing Line], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0247_a)
      Label: "She Has Some [Hom__] (head)"
    - [Off-air television recording of a documentary on Geronimo], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0022)
    - [Off-air television recording of jazz-and-blues related content], circa February 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0190)
      Label: "Black Classic - 2-9-89 and 2-16-89 / Miles Davis / Art Blakey / Wynton Marsalis / Will Women Sing the Blues"
    - [Off-air television recording of The Oscars], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0091)
    - [Off-air television recording of programs from the Comedy Central cable channel], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0289)
    - [Off-air television recording of unknown content], August 24 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0197)
    - [Off-air television recording from Channel 11 Newsreel], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0218)
      Label: Harrison Willett
    - [Off-air television recording of the CBS Presidential Debates], 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0310)
    - [Off-air television recording of unknown content], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0304)
    - [Off-air television recording of unknown content], July 15 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0296)
    - [Off-air television recording of unknown content], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0227)
    - [Commercial copy Prince: Sign O' the Times], 1987; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:25:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0039)
  - Subseries I.B. Audio, 1992-1998
    This subseries contains audio recordings from A Gathering of the Tribes events and performances dating from 1992 to 1998.
    - Jazz, by Toni Morrison, 1992; ID: 198.0161; 2 media elements 2 audiocassettes Total Running Time:; Commercial Release (Random House Audiobooks). (Box 5, Media ID: 198.0161)
    - The Poet, by Michael Connelly, 1996; ID: 198.0216; 5 media elements 5 audiocassettes Total Running Time: approx. 15:00:00 (Box 6, Media ID: 198.0216)
    - Ambush at Fort Bragg, by Tom Wolfe, 1997; ID: 198.0062; 4 media elements 4 audiocassettes Total Running Time: approx. 03:00:00; Commercial audiobook release, performed by Edward Norton (Bantam Doubleday Dell Audio Publishing). (Box 2, Media ID: 198.0062)
    - Little Evil Things, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:56:00; Commercial release (Penton Overseas, Inc.). (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0230)
    - Mrs. Ted Bliss, by Stanley Elkin, 1997; ID: 198.0145; 9 media elements 9 audiocassettes Total Running Time: 12:45:00; Commercial release (Recorded Books, Inc.). (Box 4, Media ID: 198.0145)
    - The Tao Te Ching, 1997; 1 media elements 1 audiocassette Total Running Time: 01:20:00; Commercial audiobook release, read by Nigel Hawthorne (Mystic Fire Audio). (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0212)
    - At Home in the World: A Memoir, by Joyce Maynard, 1998; ID: 198.0284; 2 media elements 2 audiocassettes; Total Running Time: Unknown; Oiginal Format: Audiocassette; Commercial release (Soundelux Audio Publishing). (Box 8, Media ID: 198.0284)